(Stuart:)Okay, I'll go.
(Stuart:)Howard, when I think about
you and Bernadette...
(Stuart:)...starting this wonderful life together...
...l can't help but get a little choked up.
l mean...
(Stuart:)...look at you, you have everything.
(Stuart:)Look at me. I'm 37...
...l sleep in the back
of a comic book store...
(Stuart:)...and I have the bone density
of an 80-year-old man.
(Leonard:)To Howard.
- Yes.
(Raj:)- Uh, who's next?
- I'll go.
(Kripke:)Howard, I'm gonna say something
to you that everybody is thinking...
...but no one has the courage
to say out loud.
When you invite a man to a bachelor party,
the implication is there will be strippers.
Maybe not completely nude...
...but at least pasties and G-strings,
that's not unreasonable.